This report is really astonishing,
since you propose a large autonomy regarding space research and development
but you make an unbelievable statement
a few lines further down,
when you say that the EU thus strengthens its cooperation and coordination with NATO
- we call it OTAN in my country -
and with the USA, calling both the wardens of security and stability in Europe — the USA!
Right after stating that the USA holds secret prisons in Europe where people are tortured!
This is absurd!
The task of the European Union has to be the demilitarization of space
because it is the next frontier, and even today's frontier of mankind,
and the multiplication of military engines
and methods of control in space is not a good thing,
all the more so because you ended your speech saying
that you intend to control the boats that take
refugees on board. All this is absurd!